## Po-Hong Chen (Phelix Chen)

Linkedin: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/kiwipower/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/kiwipower/</a>

Github: <a href="https://github.com/TWKiwi">https://github.com/TWKiwi</a>
Portfolio: <a href="https://twkiwi.github.io">https://twkiwi.github.io</a>

### Personal data

I'm a postgraduate good at Java, C#, Python development on Windows, Linux and Mac platforms. My working experiences are mostly related to web when I was working in HAMASTAR. The most representative project is "Taipei Summer Universiade volunteer registration" website. And now I'm working on data mining, machine learning and deep learning with python in my master's career. I'm researching on Fake News detection now. I am looking forward for opportunities in data analysis, algorithm, and web services.

## **Work Experience**

Douliu City, Yunlin County, National Yunlin University of Science and Technology, Yuntech Teaching Excellence Center, Part-time assistant – Oct 2017 - Nov 2017

talentpark website

Responsible for working with the school staff to understand the needs of the staff, and fine-tuning site functions and layout.

Douliu City, Yunlin County, National Yunlin University of Science and Technology,
Multimedia Database Lab.
MIS – Aug 2016 - Jun 2017

Lab website

I build a laboratory web page <u>HERE</u>. The back-end part was written by me, and theme was modified based on <u>Start Bootstrap</u>, add a few front-end library like Html, C3. And the next generator MIS refurbished download area, menu retractable components and a bit of layout adjustments. We also win a award <u>HERE</u>.

Qianzhen Dist., Kaohsiung City; HAMASTAR Technology Co., Ltd. Internship – Feb 2016 - Jul 2016

Volunteer management integration platform

Web Maintenance (RWD Upgrade)

In this five month more, I have learned lot of coding skill in web development. Such as RWD <u>HERE</u>(just update and maintenance), large web development experience <u>HERE</u>. In other hand, I'm also learning how to work with my coworker. For example, discuss with web designer your requirement, fix the bug with QA or research someone program together, presentation progress, making job handover documents and so on. I'm very enjoy in this internship.

### Education

CSIE, National Yunlin University of Science and Technology - M.S., 2016 - now

- Thesis Topic: Text Analysis and Detection on Fake News (not yet published)
- Advisor : Dr. Yin-Fu, Huang

IM, National Penghu University of Science and Technology – B.S., 2012 - 2016

# Technique

### Algorithm:

DataMining \ Collaborative Filtering \ Self-Adaptive Harmony Search \ Belief network \ Dynamic time warping \ Hidden Markov Model \ Recurrent neural networks \ Long Short-Term Memory \ Convolutional neural network etc.

#### Data Mining:

Python \ Jupyter Notebook \ Commend Line \ Tensorflow \ Keras \ NLP

#### Web Development:

C#  $\$  php  $\$  javascript  $\$  jquery  $\$  SQL  $\$  phpmyadmin  $\$  Microsoft SQL Server  $\$  Oracle MySql  $\$  ASP.Net  $\$  D3.js  $\$  C3.js  $\$  Visual Studio  $\$  TFS( in Visual Studio )  $\$  apache

### **Mobile Development:**

Java · Android Studio